Nicole O'Bomsawin

ATLANTA, GA 30307 (518) 852-8019 NICOLEOBOMSAWIN@GMAIL.COM Portfolio // LinkedIn // Github

Summary

Passionate software developer with a primary focus in MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, and Python in addition to front-end languages and frameworks. Experience collaborating on multiple web projects for small businesses and Fortune 500 global companies.

Projects

Journey - github.com/nicoleobom/Journey

Built with MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, and Google Places API Deployed with Heroku

QuizApp - github.com/nicoleobom/QuizApp

Built with MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, and custom API Deployed with Heroku

MadLibs Generator - *github.com/nicoleobom/MadLibs*

Built with Python3

Quarantini - github.com/nicoleobom/Quarantini

Built with REST APIs, HTML, and Bootstrap5

Education

FEBRUARY 2020 - AUGUST 2020

Georgia Institute of Technology - Full Stack Software Development, Certificate

Immersive 6-month software development training program that covered the MERN stack. Included React, MongoDB, SQL and MySQL, Node.js, and Express.

AUGUST 2012 - DECEMBER 2015

University at Albany, SUNY - Bachelor of Science, Business & Marketing

Experience

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Modo Modo Agency // Atlanta, GA - Senior Account Executive

- Built relationships with key clients to facilitate and help grow business
- Helped create and maintain project timelines, making sure to manage client expectations
- Wrote creative briefs and assisted in kick-off meetings for key, enterprise-level clients

APRIL 2018 - AUGUST 2019

Overit Media // Albany, NY - Account Manager

- Initiated and oversaw strategic marketing and digital campaigns for local and global clients.
- Managed client fees of over \$800k in revenue.
- Created, presented, and helped execute strategies for campaign frameworks and creative concepts.

JULY 2017 - APRIL 2018

Bluesail Marketing // Albany, NY - Co-Founder, Designer & Developer

- Designed and developed custom WordPress templates to align with each client's needs.
- Utilized Bootstrap UI framework and front-end languages like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

MARCH 2016 - JUNE 2017

Potratz Advertising // Albany, NY - Marketing Communications Manager

- Helped create a custom Facebook Messenger bot utilizing Facebook developer tools.
- Wrote and polished content for a new product launch.
- Assisted in the creation and execution of a digital strategy to increase new product sales.